The Matrix is everywhere.
Matrix heryerde
It is all around us.
Etrafımızı çevreler
Even now, in this very room.
Hatta şimdi, bu odada bile.
You can see it when you look at your window,
Pencerenden dışarı baktığında onu görebilirsin
or when you turn on your television.
Ya da televizyonunu açtığında.
You can feel it when you go to the work,
İşe gittiğinde onu hissedebilirsin...
when you go to church,
Kiliseye gittiğinde...
when you pay your taxes.
Vergilerini ödediğinde.
It is the world that has been pulled over your eyes, to blind you from the truth.
O, gözlerini boyayan,
What truth?
Ne gerçeği?
That you are a slave, Neo.
Bir köle olduğun gerçeği, Neo.
Like everyone else, you were born into bondage,
Diğer herkes gibi, sen de esaret içinde doğdun,
born into a prison that you can not smell or taste or touch.
Koklayamayacağın, tadını alamayacağın veya dokunamayacağın bir hapis içinde.
A prison...
Zihnin için bir hapis.
Unfortunately, no one can be...
Ne yazık ki, birine Matrix'in ne olduğunu anlatamazsın.
You have to see it for yourself.
Onu kendi gözlerinle görmen lazım.
This is your last chance.
Bu senin son şansın.
After this, there is no turning back.
Bundan sonra, geri dönüş yok.
You take the blue pill...
Mavi hapı alırsan,
The story ends...
Hikaye burada biter, yatağında uyanırsın,
You wake up in your bed and believe whatever you want believe.
ve inanmak istediğin şeye inanırsın.
You take the red pill,
Kırmızı hapı alırsan,
you stay in Wonderland.
Harikalar diyarında kalırsın
And I show you how deep the rabbit hole goes.
Ve sana tavşan deliğinin ne kadar derin olduğunu gösteririm
Remember...
Unutma
All I am offering is the truth, nothing more.
Sana teklif ettiğim tek şey gerçekler daha fazlası değil
Follow me.
Beni takip et